<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>


<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="xml.css"?>


<!DOCTYPE Hottest.Cities [
        <!ELEMENT name (#PCDATA)>
        <!ELEMENT  Temperature (#PCDATA)>
        <!ELEMENT description (#PCDATA)>
        ]>


<Hottest.Cities>



    <City>
        <name>Bangkok</name>
        <Temperature>104.5 degrees F (40 degrees C)</Temperature>
        <description>
            According to the World Meteorological Organization, Bangkok is the hottest
            city on the planet—not because of any particularly impressive peak temperatures,
            but because it is consistently hot all year round. The city boasts a mean annual
            temperature of 84.5 degrees F (29 degrees C), coupled with high humidity and an
            average of 128 rainy days per year; while the highest temperature on record is
            104.5 degrees F (40 degrees C). Despite Bangkok’s sticky weather, there are plenty
            of reasons to visit the capital of Thailand, ranging from iconic landmarks like
            The Grand Palace and Wat Pho (The Temple of the Reclining Buddha), to the city’s
            bustling street markets and infamous nightlife scene.
        </description>

    </City>




    <City>
        <name>Mali</name>
        <Temperature> 120 degrees F (49 degrees C)</Temperature>
        <description>
            Located on the southern edge of the Sahara Desert, the African city of Timbuktu
            is synonymous with everything remote. It’s also one of the hottest cities in
            the world, with a hot, dry climate offering record highs of 20 degrees F (49 degrees C).
            Throughout April, May and June, average maximum temperatures exceed 104 degrees F (40 degrees C).
            Modern-day Timbuktu is slowly being reclaimed by the desert and is undeniably a
            shadow of the trade hub that it once was. With a history dating back to the 12th
            century and a rich heritage of Islamic scholarship, there are still fascinating
            sights to explore within its ochre-colored walls.
        </description>

    </City>



    <City>
        <name>Ahvaz</name>
        <temperature>129 degrees F (54 degrees C)</temperature>
        <description>
            Built on the banks of the Karun River, Ahvaz is an industrial city with average highs of around
            115 degrees F (46 degrees C) during July, its warmest month. The city’s record high is a
            fever-inducing 129 degrees F (54 degrees C), making it a contender for hottest place in
            the world during the summer. Frequent sand and dust storms and an absence of rain from
            July to September compound its sky-high temperatures. Unlike the rest of Iran, there are
            few reasons to visit Ahvaz, which was ranked as the world’s most air-polluted city in
            2011; however, the riverbank offers a series of parks and bridges that make it
            both the coolest and the most scenic part of the city.
        </description>

    </City>



    <City>
        <name>Kuwait </name>
        <Temperature> 126 degrees F (52 degrees C)</Temperature>
        <description>
            This wealthy Arab metropolis is the capital of Kuwait and another contender for
            the title of one of the hottest cities in the world with average highs of over
            113 degrees F (45 degrees C) from June to August. Nightfall brings little respite,
            with after-dark low temperatures often exceeding 86 degrees F (30 degrees C)
            during the summer months. Kuwait City’s record high is 126 degrees F (52 degrees C),
            while it rains on an average of just 19 days per year. Visitors shouldn’t be put off
            by these eye-watering statistics, however, as Kuwait City offers an intriguing blend
            of past and present expressed via an eclectic roster of museums, art galleries,
            upscale malls and traditional souqs.
        </description>

    </City>



    <City>
        <name>Mecca</name>
        <Temperature> 121.6 degrees F (49.8 degrees C)</Temperature>
        <description>
            Famous as the birthplace of Muhammad, Mecca is Islam’s holiest city.
            It’s also another scorchingly hot destination, with around 22 rainy
            days per year and average annual highs of 100.5 degrees F (38 degrees C).
            The highest temperature recorded in the city is 121.6 degrees F
            (49.8 degrees C), but even in winter, average temperatures hover at a balmy 77
            degrees F (25 degrees C). Of course, the majority of Mecca’s visitors aren’t
            there for the weather—instead, millions of Muslim pilgrims arrive each year
            to perform the Hajj. The city is home to the world’s largest mosque, Masjid
            al-Haram, and the Kaaba, considered the House of Allah; however, Mecca is
            strictly off-limits to non-Muslim visitors, although that may change
            in the future once Saudi Arabia starts issuing tourist visas to non-Muslims.
        </description>

</City>





    <City>
        <name>Marrakech</name>
        <Temperature> 120 degrees F (49 degrees C)</Temperature>
        <description>
            An intoxicating riot of noise and color, semi-arid Marrakech boasts a record high of
            120 degrees F (49 degrees C). The city’s hottest months are July and August, with
            average highs exceeding 97 degrees F (36 degrees C). Although sub-freezing temperatures
            have been recorded in the winter months, Marrakech nevertheless manages to maintain
            a warm mean annual temperature of 67 degrees F (19.5 degrees C). A wider temperature
            spectrum means that visitors can choose to visit during the season that suits
            them best. Once there, there are plenty of ways to experience the city—from exploring
            the chaotic souqs of the Medina to relaxing in one of Marrakech’s famous hammam spas.
        </description>

    </City>




    <City>
        <name>Phoenix</name>
        <Temperature> 122 degrees F (50 degrees C)</Temperature>
        <description>
            Although Miami has the highest mean annual temperature of any U.S. city, the
            Arizona capital claims the hottest average highs in summer. Between 1981
            and 2010, Phoenix boasted an average of 107 days per year with a high of
            at least 100 degrees F (38 degrees C), while the city’s record high is a
            staggering 122 degrees F (50 degrees C) With approximately 300 days of
            sunshine every year, the weather alone is a good reason to visit Phoenix,
            but the Southwest city also has its fair share of theatres, galleries and
            sports stadiums. Highlights of what is sometimes the hottest place in the
            world include the Heard Museum’s Native American artworks, and the breathtaking
            flora of the Desert Botanical Garden.
        </description>

    </City>





</Hottest.Cities>